Remember that little ginger bang we used
to go to? Duh.
>> How could I forget?
>> It closed down. I had to find a new one.
>> No! They had the best naengmyeon.
>> You leaving MEKA squad feels like ages
ago.
We've all really changed since.
>> Sometimes it feels wrong that I found a
home somewhere else.
>> Hana, you didn't actually leave us. You
just grew. You're exactly where you
should be.
>> You guys sure moved on fast after I
left.
>> We changed strategies to survive, Hana.
Not because we don't miss you.
>> Well, duh.
Of course you guys miss me.
>> Don't make me take that back. The
junkers are a mess.
But you actually seem kind of smart.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Or maybe you just don't talk enough for
people to know.
>> Maybe that seems beast.
>> Sure is.
>> D.Va's cuter.
>> Fights minus enemies, but I reckon in a
past life we were thick as thieves. Just
two kittens napping on a window sill.
Meow.
>> Yeah, not even in your dreams, dude.
>> MEKA is rather clever to make soldiers
of their celebrities.
>> Uh, other way around. We're here to
protect the people, not walk a runway.
>> Hmm, perhaps. Though war can be quite
glamorous once you clear away the
rubble.
>> Finally, I've been relieved of my duty.
Now, Hana can drag you to the arcade
instead.
>> Don't be like that. It's hard for her to
find real competition to play with.
>> Wait. She sees me as real competition?
>> Yeah. But you didn't hear that from me.
>> Hana's lucky to have a friend like you
in her corner, isn't she?
>> Yeah, well, someone needs to remind her
when she needs to lock in.
>> Ah, [sighs and gasps]
I do believe Zarya said the same of me.
>> You and Hana are pretty tight now.
>> Well, girls that hit the arcade stick
together.
>> I'm a hardcore arcade girl. Does that
earn me an invite?
>> Obviously. Someone's got to bump her
into second on the leaderboards.
>> Being looked up to, seeing as a hero,
relying on.
You seem so put together.
>> The keyword there is seem. I have my
moments, too.
>> It's time to make a complaint, Gracie.
What? Your name's Gracie, too?
Sorry. You look more like a carnage.
Are there some dragons available to
rent?
>> Absolutely not.
>> Ah, I want them swirling around the new
Junkertown arena. A proper light show
for when we crown our champs.
>> Then have your foolish lackeys set off
their little fireworks.
>> Kiriko says she doesn't hate me for
lying.
But I bet she does.
>> I do not believe so.
Though, it will take time to earn her
forgiveness.
>> How long did it take for you and Hanzo?
>> We have come a long way.
But I suspect it is still a work in
progress.
>> They might let a bot run things around
here, but Junkertown would rip you to
shreds.
>> Huh. If I ever leave Japan, your little
garbage pile is the last place I'd
visit.
>> Brigitte, if you were me, how would you
make a good impression on the team?
>> Oh, that's easy. Just let them try on
your hat.
>> That's pretty good.
Wait, you're serious?
>> Well, it worked for Cassidy, so I'd say
it's worth a shot.
>> I commend you, Vera. Your company's
shielding has proven quite useful so
far.
>> Of course. Better than new armaments,
your victory is all but assured. When
Vishkar rebuilds, I expect a monument to
my leadership.
>> Consider it done, my dear. Prepare
yourself, subject Sigma. I will have
need of you soon.
>> How soon is soon when time slips away?
When moments become millennia?
>> Enough. Dr. Adia Wren will harness your
power when the time is right.
>> The harness? Yes.
Of course.
>> I just know there's something terrible
under that mask of yours.
>> None of your business.
>> Silly little piggy.
Everything I want is my business.
Even in her own keep, Shion could not
lead the Hashimoto to victory. How
beautiful.
>> Better not let her hear you talking like
that. She's killed for a lot less.
>> She could not best me.
Rage as mindless as hers
is a weakness I've long since overcome.
>> Uh-huh. Whatever you say.
>> Myko, the Wreckers want you back.
Thought you might like to know.
They'll hate that. I'll pass it along.
>> Was there ever a world where you'd have
sold us out?
>> No.
I realized pretty quick I could never
betray you guys.
>> That story about losing your arm in a
bike accident, was that a lie, too?
>> Not entirely.
There was a bike involved.
>> Still skirting around the details, huh?
>> I'm not trying to hide anything, Kiriko.
It's just
really hard to talk about. Will you
thank Nobita for letting me keep the
hat?
>> It's fine. Not like he would have made
you give it back.
>> He doesn't want to hear from me, does
he?
>> Can you blame him? You know what the
Hashimoto did to his sister.
>> One, two, three, four. Now, wait. Wait
for it.
>> [sighs]
>> Five, six, DEAD TONIGHT.
>> [laughter]
>> SO,
>> A WHOLE SHOP dedicated to your little
pet cheese here. Think they'll have that
limited edition piggy money?
>> I hope so.
>> Then you'll have it, my dear bosom
friend. I'll even threaten the shop keep
if I have to.
>> THANKS.
>> WE'RE DOING IT, MIKO. We've got a ship,
we've got a dream, and we're seeing the
world.
>> YEP.
>> WHERE TO NEXT? One of them temples in
Beijing, the sunlit shores of Santorini,
or maybe maybe even Missouri.
>> Ooh,
Missouri.
>> My biggest dream is to set off a
fantastical explosion, incinerate
everything and everyone as the place IS
BLOWN TO SMITHEREENS. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I think that sounds like a nightmare.
>> Misky did not choose his upbringing,
brother.
Try to see him for more than his
mistakes.
>> Absolutely not. He should be punished
for his failures.
>> As I was punished for mine.
>> Perhaps
a more tempered view would be best.
>> Misky. Misky.
When I get my hands on you,
whatever shall I put you through?
>> Your words don't scare me anymore.
>> Then what of my actions? How much pain
does that body of yours remember?
>> Not as much as yours will if you come
after me.